Guide to the John Holmstrom Papers and Punk Magazine Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
John Holmstrom papers and Punk magazine records
1975-2006
GEN MSS 951
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
52.34
(109 boxes) + 13 broadside folders and 1 roll
Holmstrom, John, 1954-
Scope and Contents
Correspondence, writings, photographs, maquettes, printed materials, posters, ephemera, audiovisual materials, artwork, and other records relating to Punk Magazine and John Holmstrom.
Arrangement
Organized into eight series: Series I. Artwork. Series II. Writings and Correspondence. Series III. Business Records. IV. Photographs. Series V. Printed Materials. Series VI. Merchandise. Series VII. Ephemera and Realia. Series VIII. Audiovisual Materials.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Johan Kugelberg on the Edwin J. Beinecke Book Fund and gift of John Holmstrom, 2012.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Boxes 104-119 (audiovisual materials): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Box 120 (born digital): Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Box 123 (artwork): Restricted fragile material. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
John Holmstrom
John Holmstrom (1954-) is an American writer and cartoonist. A founding editor of Punk magazine, Holmstrom also worked for publications including The Village Voice, Heavy Metal, and High Times.
Punk Magazine
Punk magazine was created by John Holmstrom, Ged Dunn, and Legs McNeill in 1975. Fifteen issues were published between 1976 and 1979, with a special issue in 1981 and additional issues published in the 2000s.
Holmstrom, John, 1954-
- Artwork, Series I
  - Punk magazine artwork
    - Punk Issue #1, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (Oversize))
    - Punk Issue #1, 1975-1976 (Box 2 (Oversize))
    - Punk Issue #1 cover, 1976 (Box 3 (Broadside))
    - Punk Issue #2, circa 1976 (Box 4 (Oversize))
    - Punk issue #2, 1976 (Box 5 (Broadside))
    - Punk issue #3, 1976 (Box 6 (Oversize))
    - Punk issue #3, 1976 (Box 7)
    - Punk issue #4, 1976 (Box 8 (Oversize))
    - Punk issue #4, 1976 (Box 9)
    - Punk issue #4, 1976 (Box 10 (Broadside))
    - Punk issue # 5, 1976 (Box 11 (Oversize))
    - Punk Issue # 5, 1976 (Box 12 (Oversize))
    - Punk issue #6, 1976 (Box 13 (Oversize))
    - Punk issue #6, 1976 (Box 14)
    - Punk issue #6, 1976 (Box 15 (Broadside))
    - Punk issue #7, 1976 (Box 16 (Broadside))
    - Punk issues #7 and #8, 1976-1977 (Box 17 (Oversize))
    - Punk issues #7, #8, and #10, 1976-1977 (Box 18)
    - Punk issue #11, 1977 (Box 19 (Oversize))
    - Punk issue #11, 1977 (Box 20)
    - Art for Punk #0 Supplement in High Times February 1977 (Box 21 (Oversize))
    - Punk issue #12, 1978 (Box 22 (Oversize))
    - Punk issue #14, 1978 (Box 23 (Oversize))
    - Punk issue #14, 1978 (Box 24)
    - Punk issue #15 (Mutant Monster Beach Party), 1978 (Box 121)
    - Punk issue #15 (Mutant Monster Beach Party), 1978 (Box 122 (Oversize))
    - Punk issue #15 (Mutant Monster Beach Party), hand-drawn maquette (Box 123 (Oversize))
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted fragile material. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
    - Punk Issue #16, 1978 (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - Punk Issue #17, 1978-1979 (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Punk Issue #17, 1978-1979 (Box 27)
    - Unpublished Punk Issue #18, Art for Punk Clanadar 1979, 1978-1979 (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Unpublished Punk Issue #18, 1979 (Box 29 (Oversize))
    - Art from Punk Special Edition: D.O.A.: The Official Filmbook, circa 1981 (Box 30 (Oversize))
    - Art from Punk Special Edition: D.O.A.: The Official Filmbook, circa 1981 (Box 31 (Oversize))
    - Miscellanious material and unpublished, circa 1976-1981 (Box 32 (Oversize))
    - Punk V.2 #0 1996 book, Punk #19, #20; miscellaneous Punk Magazine-related artwork, circa 1996-2012 (Box 33 (Oversize))
    - Punk Issues #6 (from A-13), #11 (from A-7), #14 (from A-13), #14 (from Framed), #16 (from Framed)., circa 1976-1978 (Box 34 (Oversize))
  - Other artwork
    - John Holmstrom artwork (Box 35 (Oversize))
    - John Holmstrom artwork (Box 36 (Oversize))
    - John Holmstrom artwork (Box 37 (Oversize))
    - John Holmstrom artwork (Box 38 (Oversize))
    - John Holmstrom artwork (Box 39 (Oversize))
    - John Holmstrom artwork (Box 40 (Oversize))
    - John Holmstrom artwork, 1970s-1990s (Box 41)
    - John Holmstrom artwork (Box 42 (Oversize))
    - Joe / The Joe Show (Box 43 (Oversize))
    - Joe / The Joe Show (Box 44 (Oversize))
    - Joe / The Joe Show (Box 45 (Oversize))
    - The Joe Show (Box 46 (Broadside))
    - High Times (Box 47 (Oversize))
    - Bosko (Box 48 (Oversize))
    - Hep Cat (Box 49 (Oversize))
    - Ramones album cover proofs, 1976, 1978 (Box 50 (Broadside))
- Writings and correspondence, Series II
  - Legend of Nick Detroit film project. DELETE ME?!, circa 1980 (Box 51)
  - Manuscript with corrections beginning "The Connecticut punk rock (or new wave or whatever you want to call it) scene…" Intended for Punk #18., circa 1980 (Box 52)
  - Springer, Cole, 1976 (Box 55)
  - Photocopied typescript text "Leni Riefenstal: All Singing, All Dancing, All Goosestepping" by Lou Stathis, with original corrections, published in Punk #16., 1979 (Box 52)
  - "Put 'em up or shuddup: Punk Interviews Sugar Ray Leonard.", undated (Box 52)
  - Text of record reviews by Patricia Ragan., undated (Box 52)
  - "Houston Notes" by Diego Cortez, with two attached photo slides., undated (Box 52)
  - Original ballots for the 1979 Punk Magazine Awards, with entries by Joe Stevens, John Holmstrom, Legs McNeil, Roberta Bayley, and others. (Box 52)
  - Photocopied section of Junky by William S. Burroughs, with notes., undated (Box 52)
  - Original entries to the "Punk Drunk as a Skunk" contest., undated (Box 52)
  - "Estelle + Jimmy George…" in an unknown hand., uundated (Box 52)
  - Sex Pistols tour diary, 1978 January; 1 folder (Box 52)
  - Manuscript items. SEE LIST, 1970s-1980s (Box 52)
  - see list, 1970s-2000s (Box 53)
  - Correspondence A-M, 1970s-2000s (Box 54)
  - Correspondence N-Z, unlabelled folder, 1970s-2000s (Box 55)
  - Contains at material from supplement 1 and 2, 1960s-1990s (Box 56)
  - Nick Detroit Screenplay and Notes in a spiral notebook. Beyond the screenplay draft, the notebook contains drawings, storyboards, script sections, business plans, and location and casting notes., circa 1980 (Box 51)
  - Punk #6, The Legend of Nick Detroit. Punk issue with numerous yellow post-it notes stuck to interiors. Post-its are production notes for the 1996 book Punk: The Original., circa 1976, 1996 (Box 51)
  - Typescript of The Legend of Nick Detroit., circa 1980 (Box 51)
  - The Legend of Nick Detroit film scenario, copy., circa 1980 (Box 51)
  - Partial Notes for The Legend of Nick Detroit., circa 1980 (Box 51)
  - The Legend of Nick Detroit typescript, partial with, signature on the cover page. Duplicate Xerox cover page., circa 1980 (Box 51)
  - Nick Detroit plot outline, partial., circa 1980 (Box 51)
  - The Legend of Nick Detroit screenplay, partial., circa 1980 (Box 51)
  - The Legend of Nick Detroit screenplay, partial., circa 1980 (Box 51)
  - The Legend of Nick Detroit screenplay, xerox, with correctional notes., circa 1980 (Box 51)
  - The Legend of Nick Detroit screenplay, contains MS, paste-up,and white-out corrections., circa 1980 (Box 51)
  - Folder containing The Legend of Nick Detroit screenplays, typescript with MS, white-out corrections and notes. Folder also contains MS on lined notebook paper and drawing paper with screenplay drafts, and notes., circa 1980 (Box 51)
  - Letter concerning script revisions by Sheilagh Casey, too Don Stillman from Sheilagh Casey., undated (Box 51)
  - Nick Detroit treatment on Punk stationary., undated (Box 51)
  - Nick Detroit picture budget detail., undated (Box 51)
  - Notes on the Proposed Production of The Legend of Nick Detroit, notes, production principal biographies, cast list, and cast biographies., undated (Box 51)
  - Incomplete handwritten agreement between John Holmstrom and unnamed producer., undated (Box 51)
  - Budget from Soft Focus., undated (Box 51)
  - Cover letter from John Holmstrom for Legend of Nick Detroit proposal. Addressed to, Sam Szurek, Time-Life Video, two copies, one with white-out correction., undated (Box 51)
  - Xerox of handwritten budget., undated (Box 51)
  - Agreement between Holmstrom and agent Brian Martin, undated (Box 51)
  - Variant typescript agreement between Holmstrom and agent Brian Martin, signed., undated (Box 51)
  - Picture Budget Detail, multiple versions., undated (Box 51)
  - Two copies of a cover letter for Legend of Nick Detroit screenplay, to Bob Harbin from John Holmstrom, one version on Punk stationary., undated (Box 51)
  - Xerox of a letter to Richard Hell concerning Elvis Costello's involvement in Nick Detroit., undated (Box 51)
  - Agreement with agent Brian Martin., undated (Box 51)
  - Cover letter for returned Nick Detroit synopsis and screenplay., undated (Box 51)
  - Agreement between Holmstrom & Legs McNeil with Cinema Continuum Ltd. for The Legend of Nick Detroit., undated (Box 51)
  - Scenario manuscript notes on "Wedgmoor Wollins Sample Request" stationary., undated (Box 51)
  - Typescript partial scenario for Nick Detroit., undated (Box 51)
  - Xerox of handwritten letter from Richard Hell to Elvis Costello concerning the Nick Detroit film project., undated (Box 51)
  - Bound copy of The Legend of Nick Detroit screenplay., undated (Box 51)
  - Manuscript, "So who the fuck are the Dead Boys anyway?", lettered by Sue Pellegrino., undated (Box 52)
  - Photocopied proposal for the comic strip Butnik and Periwinkle., undated (Box 52)
  - Photocopied outline of Hep Cat story "Don't Go Near the Park" by Aid McSpade., undated (Box 52)
  - Original Hep Cat outlines by Aid McSpade, with sketches., undated (Box 52)
  - Photocopied Hep Cat sketches and outlines., undated (Box 52)
  - Original manuscript letter from John Holmstrom, Hep Cat Productions to purchasers of the Hep Cat t-shirt., undated (Box 52)
  - Notebook with cover title "Stop! Financial Records for Back Issue Department with the outline of comic strip "Ratz: The Killer's Tale" at end., udated (Box 52)
  - Typescript text "Little Known Tourists Attractions/Traps" by Dale Ashmun., undated (Box 52)
  - Photocopied transcript of an interview with John Candy, from Stop #1., undated (Box 52)
  - Manuscript text beginning "John Belushi man of blubber" by "El Generalé.", undated (Box 52)
  - Photocopied lyrics to "This is the Worst Beer I've Ever Had" by Buster Poindexter, undated (Box 52)
  - "Blasting The Bowery Boy Blackout!" by Bill Yusk, with notes. Cover page and leaves 10-11 are original, 1-9 are photocopied facsimiles., undated (Box 52)
  - "Bernardberukeville Joural" by John Kelly., undated (Box 52)
  - "Milwaukee's Burning?" by A. Schickgrüber, Jr., undated (Box 52)
  - Transcript of interview "The Interview that Got Bob Marley Shot!", undated (Box 52)
  - Photocopied transcript of interview with Tom Carvel, with original annotation., undated (Box 52)
  - Signed computer printout of a memo from Legs McNeil to Suzanne relating to the "Best of Punk" book., undated (Box 52)
  - Article, "Public Enemy Number One" by Darren Ressler and Robert Dowling, about G.G. Allin)., undated (Box 52)
  - Photocopy of "Vatican Rag Revisited" by Bill Yusk, submitted to Stop Magazine., circa 1982-1983 (Box 52)
  - Photocopy of "Tarzan the Mogul: A Review of the Play Geniuses by Jonathan Reynolds" by Bill Yusk, submitted to Stop Magazine., circa 1982-1983 (Box 52)
  - "Punk of the Month" rejects", original self-submissions for "Punk of the Month", mixed manuscript and typescript, some with photo prints., undated (Box 52)
  - Manuscript text by Legs McNeil beginning "Hey your pretty smart!", and text for article "What's Wrong With This Picture" by Legs McNeil, from Punk #8., circa 1977 (Box 52)
  - Fragment of Mary Harron's interview with the Sex Pistols from Punk #8., circa 1977 (Box 52)
  - Manuscript text of Pam Brown's article on Willie "Loco" Alexander from Punk #8., circa 1977 (Box 52)
  - Manutscript text of Legs McNeil's article on the Dead Boys from Punk #7., circa 1976-1977 (Box 52)
  - "Punk of the Month" submission letter from Hal the Punk. Excerpts appeared in Punk #7, with attached cigarette wrapper., circa 1976-1977 (Box 52)
  - Original typescript of Mary Harron's article & interview with Eddie and the Hot Rods in Punk #7., circa 1976-1977 (Box 52)
  - "How to Be a Punk Groupie!" in the hand of Legs McNeil., undated (Box 52)
  - Original interview transcript with Edith Massey/"Edy the Egg Lady" in the hand of Legs McNeil, from Punk #14., 1978 (Box 52)
  - Original text of the article "Tea Party Chit-Chat with a Combat Vet Sgt. Saunders," in the hand of Legs McNeil., undated (Box 52)
  - Transcript of interview with "Billy" by "Blessed.", undated (Box 52)
  - 11 letters intended for publication in Punk #10., 1977 (Box 52)
  - "Punk of the Month" submissions labeled "#8, #7" and 6 photo prints., circa 1976-1977 (Box 52)
  - Photocopied text "Punx Pix Platters" by Peter Laugner., undated (Box 52)
  - "An Interview with Alexandro Jodorowski," compiled by Marjorie Alessandrini; translated from the French by Mary Harron, with corrections, undated (Box 53)
  - "Interview With a Holy Modal Rounder" by Ike Horn., undated (Box 53)
  - "Delinquent Debutante" by Steve Taylor: interview with Patti Smith, Lenny Kaye, Richard Sohl, and Jack Douglas, published in Punk #7 under the title "Delicate Delinquent".., circa 1976-1977 (Box 53)
  - "The Tubes" by Michele Robison, published in Punk #8., 1977 (Box 53)
  - Mary Harron's interview with Johnny Rotten, published in Punk #8., 1977 (Box 53)
  - Photocopy of the manuscript of the book My Life to Survive by Dee Dee Ramone, later published as Poison Heart, and photocopied zines created by Dee Dee Ramone., undated (Box 53)
  - Survey "Win a Free Subscription to Nerve!", completed by Lindsey Anderson., undated (Box 53)
  - Record reviews of three albums, including "Sanctuary" by the J. Geils Band, in the hand of Legs McNeil., undated (Box 53)
  - "Ike Aidnt Dead!!" in an unknown hand., undated (Box 53)
  - "O Sequel to PKM" in an unknown hand., undated (Box 53)
  - Computer-printed Bullys setlist., undated (Box 53)
  - Computer-printed text "Joey Ramone Birthday Bash Speech" by John Holmstrom., undated (Box 53)
  - Incomplete transcript of a conversation between John Holmstrom, Jolly Prochnik, and "Jiminie.", undated (Box 53)
  - Computer-printed screenplay for Hep Cat by Aid MacSpade and John Holmstrom., undated (Box 53)
  - High Times folder containing materials relating to the Hep Cat Productions., undated (Box 53)
  - Computer-printed draft of the Hep Cat screenplay by Aid MacSpade and John Holmstrom, with corrections., undated (Box 53)
  - Mixed manuscript, typescript, and photocopied material relating to the Hep Cat project. Includes sketches, treatments, formatting instructions for screenplays, resumes, and photocopied Hep Cat comic strips., undated (Box 53)
  - Computer-printed proposal for book Watch Out Punk Is Coming! By John Holmstrom and Legs McNeil., undated (Box 53)
  - Incomplete text by John Holmstrom about Punk magazine., undated (Box 53)
  - Script "The Dentist." with corrections and one handwritten leaf laid in., undated (Box 53)
  - Mailing list titled "Stop! Mailing List #8", with corrections., undated (Box 53)
  - Stop Magazine press release "New, Old Magazine; Lurid Scandal.", undated (Box 53)
  - Photocopied magazine layouts for Stop, in the hand of J.D. King., undated (Box 53)
  - Notes for Stop Magazine in the hand of John Holmstrom, under the heading "Possibilities.", undated (Box 53)
  - Lyrics beginning "All around the market place" in the hand of Aid MacSpade, from a proposal for an unidentified project., undated (Box 53)
  - Photocopied outline and proposal for the multimedia performance The Joe Show., undated (Box 53)
  - Bound "Punk Magazine Book Proposal" by John Holmstrom. Proposal for the 1996 book Punk: The Original., undated (Box 53)
  - Text beginning "The rally in North Adams, MA was a success." 1989 memo from Kathy Baker for High Times. (Box 53)
  - "The Friedman Brothers," containing a typed memo on Screw letterhead and photocopied material relating to Drew and Josh Alan Friedman., undated (Box 53)
  - text beginning "(A) Alan Arkush director ala Keith Moon." Captions in Legs McNeil's hand for the Rock 'N' Roll High School featured planned for Punk #18., undated (Box 53)
  - Review of "Come On Lets Go" by the Paley Brothers, in the hand of Legs McNeil., undated (Box 53)
  - Reviews of the Cedar Lounge and the Edge, in an unknown hand. Published in the clubs guide in Punk #16., 1979 (Box 53)
  - Reviews of Max's Kansas City and Studio 10, in the hand of Legs McNeil. Published in the clubs guide in Punk #16., 1979 (Box 53)
  - review of "Valley of the Dolls" by Generation X, in an unknown hand. Text intended for Punk #19., undated (Box 53)
  - Text beginning "Kids are people too," in an unknown hand. Text intended for Punk #19., undated (Box 53)
  - Department store reviews by "Les Izmore" (Patricia Ragan). Text intended for Punk #19., undated (Box 53)
  - "Punka-morphosis" by Jon Saltzman and Jeff Kraus., undated (Box 53)
  - Photocopied typescript text "John Rockwell, Assassin of Rock," signed "Pam Lauden.", undated (Box 53)
  - Review of Phase III (club in Pittsburgh) in an unknown hand., undated (Box 53)
  - Notes for a profile of the Ramones, in the hand of Legs McNeil., circa 1981 (Box 53)
  - Two drafts of an essay on the Ramones, the beginnings of a planned official biography, in the hand of Legs McNeil. Texts begin "Paul McCartney in 1975…" and "In 1975 Paul McCartney…", undated (Box 53)
  - Lyrics beginning "This time when I takes my vacation." Lyrics to the song "Big Fun" in the hand of Aid MacSpade; MacSpade and Holmstrom collaborated on a music video for the song in 1988. (Box 53)
  - Notes and sketches by John Holmstrom for an Alice Cooper comic book., 1973 (Box 53)
  - Typescript text of "Good" and "Bad" qualities, with attached button and business card. Typed numerology or handwriting analysis report from the Punk Magazine era., undated (Box 53)
  - "This is the floor plan (as I remember it)." Sketch of the High Times office, with names in John Holmstrom's hand., undated (Box 53)
  - "Narration. 1. Our story opens in the barren wastlands…" Original script in Legs McNeil's hand for the fumetti "The Brat Patrol" from Punk #16., 1979 (Box 53)
  - "Whatever happened to… Alvin and the Chipmunks?" by Richard Tucksmith., undated (Box 53)
  - of interview with "Mr. Weatherbea" in the hand of Legs McNeil. Originally intended for Punk #17, but unpublished., circa 1979 (Box 53)
  - "Let's try to piece together a few clues…" Text of Ron Rosenbaum's article on Tom Forcade, "The Secret Life of Tommy Rotten," published in Punk Special #1: D.O.A. Filmbook., 1981 (Box 53)
  - "The Headaches are Getting Worse: Diary of a Chippie Cabbie" by "Traviz. Bucholz"/Lester Bangs, with correction., undated (Box 53)
  - "Theresa Stern Interview" by Mary Harron, with corrections. Theresa Stern was a pseudonym for Richard Hell., undated (Box 53)
  - "An Afternoon with Iggy Pop" by Pam Brown., undated (Box 53)
  - Scripts for The Joe Show and Joe Show related ephemera., undated (Box 53)
  - Photocopied proposal for the television show "The Mighty Micro" by Sheldon Sturges., undated (Box 53)
  - Photocopied screenplay for Riff Rafferty and the Apartment of Doom by John Holmstrom and Aid MacSpade, with corrections., undated (Box 53)
  - Photocopied transcript of an interview with John Holmstrom by Dale Ashmun with notes., undated (Box 53)
  - Letter, "I trust that you have learned something…" Final leaf of a letter informing Holmstrom of his removal from the Apocalypse Players., undated (Box 53)
  - Comic strip sketch "Joe in 'The Business Appointment'" by "Happy Jack"/John Holmstrom, with prose story beginning "Any persons, places, or things in this article…" This strip and prose story are Holmstrom's first pieces using the Joe character., undated (Box 53)
  - Script "Eat, Drink, and be Merry" by John Holmstrom, script by Holmstrom for the Apocalypse Players, with notations, undated (Box 53)
  - "Joe: Good Evening, Ladies & Gent" text by Holmstrom for the Apocalypse Players., undated (Box 53)
  - Envelope labeled "Cheshire." Rating for the Apocalypse Players from the 1971 Connecticut Drama Festival with annotations. (Box 53)
  - "Marx Brothers Extravaganza." Play written by John Holmstrom for the Apocalypse players with annotations., undated (Box 53)
  - script "Salutations." Script of play performed by the Apocalypse Players, with annotations., undated (Box 53)
  - text on Rock And Roll Hall of Fame and Museum, Inc. letterhead, in John Holmstrom's hand and signed by Bill [Alt?], Assistant Curator, listing materials donated by Holmstrom to the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame., undated (Box 53)
  - "From Eileen Polk" containing a interview transcript with Cheech Marin concerning the film Rude Awakening. An unsolicited manuscript sent to High Times., undated (Box 53)
  - "Searching for UFO's in the Australian Out and In Back" by Chris Stein, with the signature of Deborah Harry. Published in Punk #14., 1978 (Box 53)
  - Photocopied sketches for the comic strip "Rusty the Cop." Holmstrom's submission to the high school publication The Spark., undated (Box 53)
  - Typed text on two index cards beginning "Side 1 (all 3 3/4)." With ms. annotations., undated (Box 53)
  - Lyrics "Everybody's Gotta Rock'n'Roll" by Joe Ckitch, on the verso contains contact information for Judy Licht; this index card relates to the story recounted in "Judy Licht's Mouth", from Punk #10., 1977 (Box 53)
  - Transcript of an interview with Paul Simenon of the Clash, in the hand of Anya Phillips., undated (Box 53)
  - Transcript of an interview with Paul Simenon of the Clash, by Anya Phillips., undated (Box 53)
  - "To whom it my [sic] concern, leave this shit alone," in the hand of Handsome Dick Manitoba., undated (Box 53)
  - "Punk Godzilla" in the hand of Legs McNeil., undated (Box 53)
  - Screenplay Loren Cass by Chris Fuller. Holmstrom appeared in the film., undated (Box 53)
  - Screenplay with first two leaves missing, opening with scene between "Dean" and "First Cowboy." Screenplay by Holmstrom's former roommate, David Allweiss, who was later convicted of the 1973 murder of Carol Hoffman., undated (Box 53)
  - Spiral notebook titled "Film notes", notes and sketches from a film class Holmstrom took. Three draft scripts for a short film entitled Bosko!, one with corrections, undated (Box 53)
  - Unidentified and manuscript material, primarily in John Holmstrom's hand., undated (Box 53)
  - Notebook of writings and sketches by Holmstrom, with heading on first leaf: "Disaster of the Decade: The Sex Pistols Tour '78." Contains Holmstrom's tour diary from the Sex Pistols 1978 tour and other writings, drawings., circa 1978 (Box 56)
  - "My Experience on the Tour – J. Holmstrom's Story" with notes and texts related to the 1978 Sex Pistols tour., undated (Box 56)
  - "Punk Transcripts #1", Includes texts, interviews, and layouts for Punk by Legs McNeil, Robert Romagnoli, John Holmstrom, Mary Harron, Bruce Carleton., undated (Box 56)
  - Review of Kongress, in the hand of Legs McNeil, written on the verso of tearsheets from National Screw., undated (Box 56)
  - Writing in the hand of Joey Ramone, beginning: "Congratulations: Holly Vincent + Jimmy Ripp Married Oct. 24 83'… Whatever happened to rebellious teenagers!!!", undated (Box 56)